### **Ezz Elden Mohamed**

#### **Full Stack Web Developer**

El Mansoura , El Dakahleya | 01002368023 , 01552282922 | ezzelden4work@gmail.com

My WebSite, linkedin , codepen , GitHub , Youtube

### **Summary**

I'm a front-end web developer. I have 5 years of experience in this field. You can say that I'm a full-time Web developer in addition to being a student. I'm passionate about keeping up with everything new in technology trends, I have my personal touch at my work. you can be keen on me for any project you need to do.

#### **Education**

I'm a student in the Delta Academy, I study at the faculty of Management Information Systems. (Final year)

#### **Skills**

Html | css | Javascript | jQuery | BootStrap | Sass | GitHub | CssAnimation | AdobeXD | Figma | React.js | Php | WordPress | PWAs

# **Professional Experience**

Atheltree Jan 2021 - Dec 2021

• Front-end Web Developer

Web Instructor: 2021

I was giving some web development courses in my college by assembling groups of students and starting how to develop the website professionally.

### **Graduation project Assistant:**

2021

I was assisting students in their graduation projects, supervising them in the design and development stages, and discussing them in front of a specialized committee of doctors in the fields of technology.

#### Some of Project:

- Elfahd Elevetor
- Smart Parking
- Elkepash

<u>The Lean</u> Jan 2020 - Jan 2021

- Front-end Web Developer
- Front-end Team Leader

#### **Afro Arab Digital**

Feb 2020 - July 2020

- Front-end Web Developer
- Front-end Team Leader

**Devolum** Feb 2018 - Feb 2020

• Front-end Web Developer

# **Projects**

Vuesax Dashboard <u>gitHub</u> <u>Live View</u>

- Chart Plugin
- Dark & Light Mode
- Chat Page

Round Base <u>gitHub</u> <u>Live View</u>

- React
- Company Review

See More Projects.....

## Langues

Arabic: Native | English: Good Write and Speak